{
    "subject": "resource/SageTV",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Inglewood,_California",
    "human_readable": "SageTV is located in Inglewood, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.90742027759552,
            "question": "Is SageTV based in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891626000404358,
            "question": "Where is SageTV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8580734729766846,
            "question": "In which city is SageTV situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8451947569847107,
            "question": "Is SageTV based in a Californian city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8161882162094116,
            "question": "Which city in California houses SageTV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7299277782440186,
            "question": "What state is SageTV in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6553031802177429,
            "question": "Where can you find the headquarters of SageTV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5995137095451355,
            "question": "To which city does SageTV belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5832542181015015,
            "question": "What is the location of SageTV's operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.421741783618927,
            "question": "What US state is home to SageTV?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=SageTV is located in Inglewood, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3249_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the location of SageTV's operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3249_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which city does SageTV belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3249_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find the headquarters of SageTV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3249_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3249_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports this triple. The text states that \"SageTV is located in Inglewood, United States.\" which implies that it is also located in California, as Inglewood is a city in California."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information from the documents supports the statement that SageTV is located in Inglewood, California. Multiple documents mention SageTV's location as Inglewood, California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}